

SUMMARY

I am a proficient SAP Consultant with 8 years of experience working both on maintenance and implementations. With a proven record on both communicating and negotiating with customers, I am used to deal with due dates, scopes, and related project difficulties. I am a team player, with skills to work both with functional and technical teams.

PERSONAL DETAILS

MOBILE +5491124047195

ADDRESS

Gelly y Obes 449, San Miguel, Buenos Aires, **Argentina**

E-MAIL gisbert.ra@gmail.com



Talent Recruiting

Ricardo **Gisbert**

SAP FICO CONSULTANT

WORK EXPERIENCE

SAP FI CO PS Consultant

Feb 2023 - Current

Working on an SAP S4 (v 2021) rollout, responsible for FI, CO and PS modules E2E for new company codes.

SAP CO Consultant

Nov 2021 - Feb 2023

Worked for an SAP S4 (v 2021) greenfield implementation for a group of automotive factories.

Previously worked on CFIN, doing improvements and new configurations.

SAP FICO Consultant

Oct 2019 - Nov 2021

Nov 2020 - Nov 2021, SAP FICO Consultant SAP FICO maintance, mainly FI- GL, FI- TX, FI- AP. Oct 2019 - Feb 2021, SAP CO Functional Lead SAP S4 (v 1909) greenfield implementation, for a group of mattress factories.

May 2019 - Oct 2019 SAP FICO Consultant

COGNIZANT - XCEL ENERGY

Maintenance FI- GL, CO, PS, Idocs

Nov 2018 - May 2019 **SAP CO Consultant**

ACCENTURE

SAP S4 (v 1709) greenfield implementation, for an oil company.

Ago 2017 - Sep 2017 SAP CO Instructor

Official SAP Academy Instructor

Sep 2015 - Oct 2018 **SAP FICO Consultant**

IBM, INDRA, SEIDOR

Worked on several assigments for different clients, mainly FI, CO, PS, RE- FX

Financial Analyst, In-house CO consultant

Jan 2006 - Set 2015

VOTORANTIM GROUP

Worked 4 years as financial analyst, 3 years as controlling analyst, and the last 2 years as an inhouse CO consultant.

EDUCATION

Associate Degree in Computer Science GENERAL SARMIENTO NATIONAL UNIVERSITY

2014 - 2019

SAP Certified Application Associate -Management Accounting (CO) with SAP **ERP 6.0 EhP6**

SAP FOUCATION

Jun 2015